Congratulations! If you are watching this video
it means that you want to learn Go,  the language developed at Google to solve Google size problems.
So what is Go good for? Go is good for Web services at scale, networking, massively concurrent applications,
operating systems, automation, and command-line tools or cryptography. Go is by design, expressive, comprehensible,
sophisticated, yet clean, clear and easy to read.
Go is on a trajectory to become the next enterprise programming language.
In a nutshell, Go provides you high performers like C and C++, super efficient, concurrency friendly
like a Java, but also fun to code like Python.
Cutting edge technologies and software are already written in Go, for example, Docker, Kubernetes
or Ethereum.
In addition to Google, which uses Go widely in production, Go is used by Uber, Netflix, Pinterest,
Slack, SoundCloud and so many more. Go is based on real-world experience and its focus is on a larger
scale engineering. The language has amazing credentials.
Google hired experienced software industry veterans like Rob Pike and Ken Thompson, who played a
major role in the invention of Unix, C, and parts of Unicode encoding scheme many decades ago.
Another Go contributor was Robert Griesemer, who studied under the creator of Pascals and has decades
of experience around compilers and garbage collection
after working on virtual machines for JavaScript in Java. According to the Stack Overflow Survey for
2020 Go is the second paying technology in the United States. Learning Go language programming could be
the best decision of your career.
So what are you waiting for?
Start your Go journey today and you'll never regret it!